ALES Records 5225
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 1959 - White Collar Workshops - Recruiting (Weekend Institutes) (Box 101, Folder 52)
- 1959 - White Collar Workshops - Recruiting (Five-Day School) (Box 101, Folder 53)
- Refusals 1959 WCW Weekend Institute (Box 101, Folder 54)
- 1959 - Promotion - Recruiting - WCW (Box 101, Folder 55)
- 1959- WCW Weekend Institute - Recruiting (Box 101, Folder 56)
- 1958 - WCW Weekend Institutes - Recruiting (Box 101, Folder 57)
- 1958 - White Collar Workshops - Recruiting (Box 101, Folder 58)
- WCW - Recruiting - Folders, Form Letters - Application Blanks etc. 1958 (Box 101, Folder 59)
- 1958 - White Collar Workshops - Recruiting (Box 101, Folder 60)
- WCW - Promotion - Recruiting - 1957 (Box 101, Folder 61)
- WCW - Recruiting - 1957 Folders, Blanks, Releases, etc. (Box 101, Folder 62)
- WCW - Promotion - Recruiting - 1958 (Box 101, Folder 63)
- 1956 - WCW Promotion A. Paston (Box 101, Folder 64)
- WCW - Promotion - 1956 (Box 101, Folder 65)
- WCW - Recruiting - 1956 (Box 101, Folder 66)
- WCW Applications Withdrawn - 1956-57, 1960, 1956-1960 (Box 101, Folder 67)
- Reports of SSOW 1951-1960 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Reports of SSOW 1941-1950 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- Reports of SSOW 1933-1940 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Student Backgrounds - All years, 1935-1948 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- White Collar Workshops, 1955-1956 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- SSOW (Box 102, Folder 6)
- White Collar Workshops - Announcements, Blanks, Forms Letters, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- 1959 WCW Weekend Institute Form Letters, Announcements, Appl'n Blanks (Box 103, Folder 2)
- 1959 White Collar Workshops 5-Day School Form Letters, Announcements, Appl'n Bills (Box 103, Folder 3)
- WCW Weekend Institute Form Letters, Releases, etc. 1958 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Applications for Admission White Collar Workshops, 1961 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- White Collar Workshops Participants A-Z:- July 1960 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Adams, Jane - WCW Weekend Institutes, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Black, Morris - WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Brown, Lewis WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Clark, Charles T. Cooper, Paul L. WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Gladstone, Lillian WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Harwig, Sue WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Hayes, Anne WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- King, Anna E. Josephs, Rica H. WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Kurahara, Roy - WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- Loughrey, Lucy K. WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- McElhearn, Arthur J. WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- Moss, Theda WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- Norwalk, Sylvia WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- Owens, Sarale 1959 WCW Weekend Institute (Box 103, Folder 20)
- Pierce, Mrs. Beatrice WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- Preston, Agnes WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 22)
- Robbins, Lillian D. WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 23)
- Rogers, Muriel Nelson WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- Science, Albert R. WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 25)
- Science, Albert R. WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 26)
- Segal, Bernice Taylor WCW Weekend Institute, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 27)
- Siff, Hilda 1959 WCW Weekend Institute (Box 103, Folder 28)
- Slonim, Phyllis A. WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 29)
- Smith, Mrs. Ernest H. WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 30)
- Strong, Raymond and Mrs. Strong WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 31)
- Tropp, Joan WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 32)
- Vandenburg, Mary WCW Weekend Institute 1959 (Box 103, Folder 33)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Persons who did not come - 1959 (Box 103, Folder 34)
- Crowell 3rd, Samuel B. WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 35)
- Dawkins, Hugh B. WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 36)
- DeNardo, Joseph WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 37)
- Dieterich, Robert E. WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 38)
- Frillman, June Ann 5-Day School WCW, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 39)
- Fuchs, John - WCW 1959 5-Day School (Box 103, Folder 40)
- Fulton, Jr., Jesse J. (did not attend) WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 41)
- Glibota, Andrew WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 42)
- Hanley, Anne F. (Mrs.) - (did not attend) WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 43)
- Herman, Clifford J. WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 44)
- Johnson, Edwin H. (Mrs.) WCW 5-Day, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 45)
- Knechtl, Genevieve 5-Day School WCW, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 46)
- Maguire, Joseph WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 47)
- Mosher, Willard A. WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 48)
- O'Dell, Kenneth 1959 WCW 5-Day School (Box 103, Folder 49)
- Paitchell, Howard WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 50)
- Osborne, Alma C. WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 51)
- Singer, Ann (did not attend) WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 52)
- Owens, Sarale WCW 5-Day School, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 53)
- Bedford, George J. WCW 5-Day School, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 54)
- Belack, Eleanor Correspondence WCW 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 55)
- Boyle, Leonard E. (Deceased) WCW 5-Day School 1958 (Box 103, Folder 56)
- Braunfeld, Leonard WCW 5-Day School Correspondence 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 57)
- Dieterich, Robert E. Correspondence WCW 5-Day School 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 58)
- Formont, Anne Correspondence WCW 5-Day School 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 59)
- Fulton, Jr., Jesse J. 5-Day School WCW 1958 (Box 103, Folder 60)
- Hanley, Mrs. Anne F. Correspondence WCW 5-Day School, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 61)
- Hauser, Jr., George H. Correspondence WCW 5-Day School 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 62)
- Holsopple, Sheldon Correspondence WCW 5-Day School, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 63)
- Hull, Donald J. Correspondence WCW 5-Day School 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 64)
- Jan, Norman WCW 5-Day School 1959 Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 65)
- Johnson, Mrs. Gloria WCW 5-Day School 1958 1959 Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 66)
- Knechtl, Genevieve WCW 5-Day School 1958 1959 Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 67)
- LaMonte, James WCW 5-Day School 1959 Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 68)
- Mosher, Willard A. WCW 5-Day School 1958 1959 Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 69)
- WCW - Alabama - 1956-1957 (Box 103, Folder 70)
- WCW Alabama 1955 (Box 103, Folder 71)
- White Collar Institute - Birmingham, Ala. Correspondence March 14-15, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 72)
- White Collar Workshop - Dec. 3-5, 1954 Sheffield, Ala. Notes, Statistics. Etc. (Box 103, Folder 73)
- White Collar Workshop - Sheffield, Ala. - Dec. 3-5, 1954 Correspondence (Box 103, Folder 74)
- White Collar Institute - Birmingham, Ala. Programs, Statistics March 15-16, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 75)
- WCW California 1956-1961 (Box 103, Folder 76)
- WCW - Colorado - 1956-1958 (Box 103, Folder 77)
- WCW - Colorado - 1955 (Box 103, Folder 78)
- WCW - Connecticut - 1959 - (Box 103, Folder 79)
- WCW - Weekend Institute: Connecticut, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 80)
- WCW - Connecticut - 1956-1957 (Box 103, Folder 81)
- WCW - Connecticut 1955 (Box 103, Folder 82)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Delaware 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 83)
- WCW - District of Columbia - 1960 (Box 103, Folder 84)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - District of Columbia - 1959 (Box 103, Folder 85)
- WCW - District of Columbia - 1959 (Box 103, Folder 86)
- WCW - District of Columbia - 1955/1958 (Box 103, Folder 87)
- WCW - Florida - 1956-1958 (Box 103, Folder 88)
- WCW - Georgia - 1955-1957 (Box 103, Folder 89)
- WCW - Illinois - 1959-1962 (Box 103, Folder 90)
- WCW - Illinois 1955-1958 (Box 103, Folder 91)
- Gilmore, Marguerite White Collar Workshops 1953-1957 (Box 103, Folder 92)
- WCW - Indiana - 1956-1960 (Box 103, Folder 93)
- WCW - Iowa - 1955-1957 (Box 103, Folder 94)
- WCW - Kansas - 1954-1960 (Box 103, Folder 95)
- WCW - Kentucky - 1955-1960 (Box 103, Folder 96)
- WCW Louisiana, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 97)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Maryland 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 98)
- WCW - Weekend Institute: Maryland 1958 (Box 103, Folder 99)
- WCW - Maryland - 1956-1958 (Box 103, Folder 100)
- WCW Maryland 1955 (Box 103, Folder 101)
- WCW - New Jersey - 1955-1957 (Box 103, Folder 102)
- WCW Maryland 1955 (Box 103, Folder 103)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Massachusetts 1959 (Box 103, Folder 104)
- WCW Maryland 1955 (Box 103, Folder 105)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Massachusetts 1959 (Box 103, Folder 106)
- WCW - Massachusetts - 1959 (Box 103, Folder 107)
- WCW - Weekend Institutes: Massachusetts 1958 (Box 103, Folder 108)
- WCW - Massachusetts - 1960 (Box 103, Folder 109)
- WCW - Massachusetts - 1960 (Box 103, Folder 110)
- WCW Massachusetts - 1955-1958 (Box 103, Folder 111)
- WCW - Michigan - 1960 (Box 103, Folder 112)
- WCW - Michigan - 1959 (Box 103, Folder 113)
- WCW - Michigan - 1955-1958 (Box 103, Folder 114)
- WCW - Minnesota 1955-1960 (Box 103, Folder 115)
- WCW - Missouri - 1955-1960 (Box 103, Folder 116)
- WCW - New Hampshire - 1957-1960 (Box 103, Folder 117)
- WCW - New Hampshire - 1957-1960 (Box 103, Folder 118)
- WCW - New Jersey - 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 119)
- WCW - New Jersey - 1958 (Box 103, Folder 120)
- WCW - New Jersey - 1959-1960 (Box 103, Folder 121)
- WCW - New Jersey - 1958 (Box 103, Folder 122)
- WCW - Weekend Institute: New Jersey 1958 (Box 103, Folder 123)
- WCW - Weekend Institute: New Jersey 1958 (Box 103, Folder 124)
- 1959 - WCW Weekend Institute - New York (Box 104, Folder 1)
- WCW - New York City - 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- WCW - New York State - 1960-1961 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- WCW - New York State - 1959 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- WCW - New York City - 1959 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- WCW - New York - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- WCW - Weekend Institute: New York, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- WCW - New York - 1956-57, 1956-1957 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- WCW - New York, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- WCW - North Carolina 1956-1960 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- WCW - Ohio - 1960 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Ohio 1959 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- WCW - Ohio - 1959 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- WCW - Ohio - 1955-1958 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- WCW - Oregon (Box 104, Folder 15)
- WCW - Pennsylvania - 1960 - (Box 104, Folder 16)
- WCW - Pennsylvania - 1959 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- WCW - Pennsylvania - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 18)
- WCW - Weekend Institute: Pennsylvania, 1958 (Box 104, Folder 19)
- WCW - Pennsylvania - 1955-1956 (Box 104, Folder 20)
- WCW - Rhode Island - 1955-1960 (Box 104, Folder 21)
- WCW - South Carolina - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 22)
- WCW - South Dakota - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 23)
- WCW - South Dakota - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 24)
- WCW - Tennessee - 1956-1960 (Box 104, Folder 25)
- WCW Texas - 1960 (Box 104, Folder 26)
- TVA White Collar Workshop - Gatlinburg, Tennessee Correspondence - 1956 (Box 104, Folder 27)
- WCW - Virginia - 1955-56, 1960, 1955-1960 (Box 104, Folder 28)
- WCW - Washington - 1956-1957 (Box 104, Folder 29)
- WCW - West Virginia - 1957 - (Box 104, Folder 30)
- WCW - Wisconsin - 1955-1957 (Box 104, Folder 31)
- WCW - Canada - 1960 - (Box 104, Folder 32)
- WCW - Canada - 1959 (Box 104, Folder 33)
- WCW - Canada - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 34)
- WCW - Foreign - 1957 - (Box 104, Folder 35)
- TVA White Collar Workshop - Program, statistics, etc. - Jan. 29- Feb. 3 1956 (Box 104, Folder 36)
- White Collar Workshops - Materials - 1961 (Box 104, Folder 37)
- 1960 - White Collar Workshops - Library (Box 104, Folder 38)
- 1960 White Collar Workshops Library (Box 104, Folder 39)
- 1959 - White Collar Workshops - Library (Box 104, Folder 40)
- WCW - Materials - Bibliography on Labor, composed at Social Workers Institutes, July 1958 (Box 104, Folder 41)
- WCW - Library - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 42)
- White Collar Bibliography - 1955 (Box 104, Folder 43)
- 1957 - White Collar Workshops - Library (Box 104, Folder 44)
- White Collar Bibliography - 1955 (Box 104, Folder 45)
- 1957 - White Collar Workshops - Library (Box 104, Folder 46)
- Requests for Material - White Collar Workshops - 1957 (Box 104, Folder 47)
- 1956 - White Collar Workshops - Library (Box 104, Folder 48)
- Requests for Material - White Collar Workshops - 1956 (Box 104, Folder 49)
- Requests for Material - White Collar Workshops - 1956 (Box 104, Folder 50)
- 1955 White Collar Workshops - Library (Box 104, Folder 51)
- White Collar Workshops - FILM, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 52)
- Requests for Material White Collar Workshops, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 53)
- 1954 White Collar Workshops - Library (Box 104, Folder 54)
- WCW - Library - 1953 (Box 104, Folder 55)
- WCW - Library - 1953 (Box 104, Folder 56)
- WCW - Requests for Material 1953 (Box 104, Folder 57)
- WCW - Library - 1952 (Box 104, Folder 58)
- WCW - - Requests for Material 1952 (Box 104, Folder 59)
- WCW - Requests for Material 1952 (Box 104, Folder 60)
- WCW - Library - 1951 (Box 104, Folder 61)
- White Collar Workshops - Requests for Material 1951 (Box 104, Folder 62)
- White Collar Workshops - Housing (Princeton) - 1951 (Box 104, Folder 63)
- WCW - Housing Facilities - 1961 (Box 104, Folder 64)
- WCW - Housing at Sarah Lawrence - 1960 (Box 104, Folder 65)
- 1959 White Collar Workshops 5-Day School Housing (Box 104, Folder 66)
- White Collar Workshops - Housing - 1958 (Box 104, Folder 67)
- White Collar Workshops - Sarah Lawrence College - 1957 (Box 104, Folder 68)
- 1956 - White Collar Workshops - Location (Box 104, Folder 69)
- Location - White Collar Workshops - 1955 (Box 104, Folder 70)
- White Collar Workshops - Housing - Sarah Lawrence College 1955 (Box 104, Folder 71)
- 1954 - Housing at Sarah Lawrence College (Box 104, Folder 72)
- 1953 WCW - Location (Box 104, Folder 73)
- 1953 WCW - Location (Box 104, Folder 74)
- White Collar Workshops Location - 1954 (Box 104, Folder 75)
- White Collar Workshops - Sarah Lawrence College - Housing - 1953 (Box 104, Folder 76)
- White Collar Workshops Housing - 1952 (Box 104, Folder 77)
- White Collar Workshops - Housing - 1951 (Box 104, Folder 78)
- Student Reports - White Collar Workshops 1953 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- White Collar Workshops - Pilot Study 1958 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Faculty Reports on Student Records White Collar Workshops - 1956 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Faculty Reports - 1948, 1949 - (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Faculty Reports - 1938-1942 - 1943 and 1947, 1938-1947 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- 1960 White Collar Workshops Notes (Box 105, Folder 6)
- 1961 White Collar Workshops Statistics, List of Participants (Box 105, Folder 7)
- 1960 White Collar Workshops Statistics (Box 105, Folder 8)
- 1960 White Collar Workshops Statistics (Box 105, Folder 9)
- 1959 WCW Weekend Institute Statistics (Box 105, Folder 10)
- WCW - Statistics - 1957 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- 1959 White Collar Workshops 5-Day School Statistics (Box 105, Folder 12)
- 1958 - White Collar Workshops - Statistics (Box 105, Folder 13)
- 1956 White Collar Workshops - Statistics (Box 105, Folder 14)
- 1955 White Collar Workshops - Statistics (Box 105, Folder 15)
- 1954 White Collar Workshops - Statistics (Box 105, Folder 16)
- WCW - Statistics - 1953 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Statistics 1952 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- WCW Statistics 1951 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- WCW Statistics 1950 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- SSOW Statistics 1949 (Box 105, Folder 21)
- SSOW Statistics 1948 (Box 105, Folder 22)
- SSOW Statistics 1947 (Box 105, Folder 23)
- SSOW Statistics 1946 (Box 105, Folder 24)
- SSOW Statistics - 1945 (Box 105, Folder 25)
- SSOW Statistics 1941-1944 (Box 105, Folder 26)
- TVA White Collar Workshops Gatlinburg, Tennessee Jan. 29 - Feb. 3, 1956 (Box 105, Folder 27)
- Speakers and Guests - 1956 - White Collar Workshops (Box 105, Folder 28)
- 1955 - White Collar Workshops - Faculty and Staff (Box 105, Folder 29)
- White Collar Workshops - Speakers and Guests - 1954 (Box 105, Folder 30)
- Faculty and Staff - WCW - 1954 (Box 105, Folder 31)
- White Collar Workshops - Faculty and Staff 1953 (Box 105, Folder 32)
- Speakers and Guests - WCW - 1952 (Box 105, Folder 33)
- WCW - Faculty and Staff - 1951 (Box 105, Folder 34)
- White Collar Workshops - Faculty - 1961 (Box 105, Folder 35)
- 1960 - WCW - Institute Faculty (Box 105, Folder 36)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Report - 1959 (Box 105, Folder 37)
- 1959 - WCW Weekend Institute - Faculty (Box 105, Folder 38)
- 1959 - Faculty - White Collar Workshops (Box 105, Folder 39)
- White Collar Workshops - Correspondence re Student Assistants - 1959 (Box 105, Folder 40)
- WCW Invited Guests - 1958 (Box 105, Folder 41)
- 1958 - Faculty and Staff - WCW (Box 105, Folder 42)
- WCW - Faculty and Staff - 1957 (Box 105, Folder 43)
- WCW - Speakers and Guests - 1957 (Box 105, Folder 44)
- Faculty and Staff - WCW - 1956 (Box 105, Folder 45)
- White Collar Workshops - September 1961 - Transcript of Tapes of Session (Box 105, Folder 46)
- White Collar Workshops Project - Attitudinal Questionnaires - 1958 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- 1959 White Coillar Workshops 5-Day School at School - Given-Out Materials (Box 106, Folder 2)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Planning Meetings 1958 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Planning Meetings 1958 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Social Impact and Unemployment - 1958 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- WCW - Weekend Institute Allegations - 1958 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Refusals - 1958 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- 1958 - WCW Weekend Institute Reports, Findings, etc. (Box 106, Folder 8)
- WCW Weekend Institute Reports, Findings, etc. - 1958 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- WCW - Weekend Institute - Correspondence with Students 1958 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- WCW - Automation Institute - 1956 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- WCW - Automation Institute - 1956 (Box 106, Folder 12)
- White Collar Workshops - Material Distributed to Students, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 13)
- 1957 - Publicity - WCW (Box 106, Folder 14)
- WCW - Publicity - 1959 (Box 106, Folder 15)
- WCW - Publicity - 1956 (Box 106, Folder 16)
- WCW Publicity 1955 (Box 106, Folder 17)
- Theatre Benefit Folder 2 - 1962 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Benefit 1961 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- WCW Theatre Benefit 1961 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- WCW Theatre Benefit - 1959 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- SSOW Theatre Benefit 1958 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- SSOW Theatre Benefit 1957 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- WCW Theatre Benefit 1956 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- WCW Theatre Benefit 1955 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- WCW Benefit 1954 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- WCW Benefit 1953 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- WCW Benefit 1952 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- WCW Theatre Benefit 1951 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- SSOW Theatre Party Benefit 1950 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- SSOW Benefit 1948-49, 1948-1949 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- SSOW Benefit 1947 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- SSOW - Theatre Benefit 1945 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- SSOW - Finance Theatre Benefit - 1944 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- The Bishop Robert L. Paddock Estate, 1943 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- Samuel S. Fels Fund - SSOW Finance, 1944 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- Appeal to Foundations for the Summer school for Office Workers, 1948 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- WCW Smith College 1960-1962 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- WCW Smith College 1956-59, 1956-1959 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- Smith College 1952-1955 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- Smith College - Northampton - 1938-1951 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- Contact: Universities and Colleges Smith College, 1962 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- Funds - Colleges: Smith, Wellesley, Vassar SSOW, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 26)
- White Collar Workshops Finance, 1961 (Box 107, Folder 27)
- White Collar Workshops Finance 1960 (Box 107, Folder 28)
- 1959 - White Collar Workshops - Finance (Box 107, Folder 29)
- 1958 - White Collar Workshops - Finance (Box 107, Folder 30)
- 1957 - White Collar Workshops - Finance (Box 107, Folder 31)
- 1956 - White Collar Workshops - Finance (Box 107, Folder 32)
- WCW - Finance - 1955 (Box 107, Folder 33)
- WCW - Finance -1954 (Box 107, Folder 34)
- 1953 Finance - WCW (Box 107, Folder 35)
- SSOW Finance - 1952 (Box 107, Folder 36)
- SSOW Finance 1951 (Box 107, Folder 37)
- SSOW Finance Letters 1950 (Box 107, Folder 38)
- SSOW Finance 1949 (Box 107, Folder 39)
- SSOW Finance 1948 (Box 107, Folder 40)
- SSOW Finance 1948 (Box 107, Folder 41)
- SSOW Finance Contributors - 1947 (Box 107, Folder 42)
- SSOW Finance 1946 (Box 107, Folder 43)
- SSOW Finance 1945 (Box 107, Folder 44)
- SSOw Finance 1944 (Box 107, Folder 45)
- SSOW Finance 1943 (Box 107, Folder 46)
- SSOW Finance 1942 (Box 107, Folder 47)
- SSOW Finance Appeals 1941 (Box 107, Folder 48)
- SSOW Finance 1940 (Box 107, Folder 49)
- SSOW Finance 1939 (Box 107, Folder 50)
- SSOW Finance Appeals 1938 (Box 107, Folder 51)
- SSOW Finance Appeals 1937 (Box 107, Folder 52)
- SSOW Finance Appeals 1936 (Box 107, Folder 53)
- SSOW Finance 1935 (Box 107, Folder 54)
- SSOW Finance 1934 (Box 107, Folder 55)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School 1921-1922 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Publicity - Bryn Mawr-Hudson Shore, 1922-1933 (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School 1921-1922 Reports (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Address by Letta Perkins on Bryn Mawr Summer School 1922 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Syllabi - Bryn Mawr Summer School 1932-1933 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School 1923-1933 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Syllabi - Bryn Mawr 1921-1931 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Bryn Mawr School Syllabi, 1935 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Findings of Household Employees Group Bryn Mawr - 1937 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Findings of Household Employees Group Bryn Mawr - 1937 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Article on Bryn Mawr Summer School Christian Register, March 1937 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School - Magazine 1938 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Hudson Shore - Syllabi 1936-1938 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School Magazine - Shop and School = 1923-1924 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School 1934-1938 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Bryn Mawr Summer School 1934-1938 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Report - Labor Dramatics Bryn Mawr Summer School 1932 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Report - Labor and Democracy in the Home Hudson Shore Labor School 1942 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Hudson Shore Labor School - Magazine 1941, 1942 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- "They Say" - Hudson Shore, 1940 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Hudson Shore Labor School 1940-1950 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Hudson Shore Labor School 1940-1950 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Hudson Shore Labor School 1940-1950 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Hudson Shore Labor School 1939 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Hudson Shore 1921-1949 by Margaret Wood (from WEB News Letter 1949) (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Hudson Shore Labor School - Magazine 1947 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Report of Leadership Training Workshop Hudson Shore Labor School August 1948 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Vineyard Shore School 1926-1932 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Barnard School 1927-1932 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Affiliated Summer Schools for Women Workers in Industry - Barnard. Bryn Mawr, Wisconsin April - 1929 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Barnard School - Syllabi 1927-1933 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Misc., 1929 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- LMDC Letterhead, 1943 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- Workers' Service Program W.F.A., 1940 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- National Committee for the Extension of Labor Education 1945-1950 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- Catalog - Workers Education Archives, 1921-1951 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 1, 1957 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  Reel
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 2, 1957 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 3, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 4, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 5)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 5, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 6)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 6, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 7, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 8, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 9, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 10, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 11, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- A.L.E.S. Papers Reel 12, 1940-1950 (Box 110, Folder 13)